PYTHON IMPLEMENTATION OF SCHELLING'S MODEL OF SEGREGATION
Start Time: 2023-07-09 19:56:10.993396


START: Loading data grid. ...
 DONE: Loading data grid.

Grid Dimensions:
> Row count: 10
> Column count: 10

Data Grid:
X X O O X O X O X O
X O O X O X O X O X
O X X   X O O X O X
O X X X O O X   X O
X O O X O X O X X O
X O X   X X O   O X
X X O O X O X O X O
X O   O X O O X O O
O X X X O O   O X O
O O O O O O O X O X


START: Computing Index of Dissimilarity v1
Subregion size: 4 x 4

Subregion:
X X O O
X O O X
O X X  
O X X X

Index of Dissimilarity = 0.09 or 0.09
DONE: Computing Index of Dissimilarity.


START: Simulation of Schelling Segregation.


DONE: Simulation of Schelling Segregation.



End Time: 2023-07-09 19:56:11.026390
