PYTHON IMPLEMENTATION OF SCHELLING'S MODEL OF SEGREGATION
Start Time: 2023-07-09 19:37:31.852353


START: Loading data grid. ...
 DONE: Loading data grid.

Grid Dimensions:
> Row count: 10
> Column count: 10


START: Printing data contents.

X X O O X O X O X O
X O O X O X O X O X
O X X   X O O X O X
O X X X O O X   X O
X O O X O X O X X O
X O X   X X O   O X
X X O O X O X O X O
X O   O X O O X O O
O X X X O O   O X O
O O O O O O O X O X

DONE: Printing data contents.


START: Computing Index of Dissimilarity v1
Subregion size: 4 x 4

Subregion:
X X O O
X O O X
O X X  
O X X X

Index of Dissimilarity = 0.09 or 0.09
DONE: Computing Index of Dissimilarity.


START: Computing Index of Dissimilarity v2.

Subregion:
[['X' 'O' 'X' 'O']
 ['O' 'X' 'O' 'X']
 ['O' 'X' 'O' 'X']
 ['X' ' ' 'X' 'O']]
X O X O
O X O X
O X O X
X   X O

Index of Dissimilarity = 0.575698 or 0.58
DONE: Computing Index of Dissimilarity.


START: Simulation of Schelling Segregation.


DONE: Simulation of Schelling Segregation.



End Time: 2023-07-09 19:37:31.856357
