START: Loading data grid. ...
 DONE: Loading data grid.

Grid Dimensions:
> Row count: 20
> Column count: 37


START: Printing data contents.

X X O O X O X O X O X X O O X O X O X X X O O X O X O X O X X O O X O X O
X O O X O X O X O X X O O X O X O X O X O O X O X O X O X X O O X O X O X
O X X   X O O X O X O X X   X O O X O O X X   X O O X O X O X X   X O O X
O X X X O O X   X O O X X X O O X   X O X X X O O X   X O O X X X O O X O
X O O X O X O X X O X O O X O X O X X X O O X O X O X X O X O O X O X O X
X O X   X X O   O X X O X   X X O   O X O X   X X O   O X X O X   X X O O
X X O O X O X O X O X X O O X O X O X X X O O X O X O X O X X O O X O X O
X O   O X O O X O O X O   O X O O X O X O   O X O O X O O X O   O X O O X
O X X X O O   O X O O X X X O O   O X O X X X O O   O X O O X X X O O   O
O O O O O O O X O X O O O O O O O X O O O O O O O O X O X O O O O O O O X
X X O O X O X O X O X X O O X O X O X X X O O X O X O X O X X O O X O X O
X O O X O X O X O X X O O X O X O X O X O O X O X O X O X X O O X O X O X
O X X   X O O X O X O X X   X O O X O O X X   X O O X O X O X X   X O O X
O X X X O O X   X O O X X X O O X   X O X X X O O X   X O O X X X O O X O
X O O X O X O X X O X O O X O X O X X X O O X O X O X X O X O O X O X O X
X O X   X X O   O X X O X   X X O   O X O X   X X O   O X X O X   X X O O
X X O O X O X O X O X X O O X O X O X X X O O X O X O X O X X O O X O X O
X O   O X O O X O O X O   O X O O X O X O   O X O O X O O X O   O X O O X
O X X X O O   O X O O X X X O O   O X O X X X O O   O X O O X X X O O   O
O O O O O O O X O X O O O O O O O X O O O O O O O O X O X O O O O O O O X

DONE: Printing data contents.


START: Computing Index of Dissimilarity.

Subregion:
X X O O X O X O X O
X O O X O X O X O X
O X X   X O O X O X
O X X X O O X   X O
X O O X O X O X X O
X O X   X X O   O X
X X O O X O X O X O
X O   O X O O X O O
O X X X O O   O X O
O O O O O O O X O X

Index of Dissimilarity = 0.330565 or 0.33
DONE: Computing Index of Dissimilarity.


START: Simulation of Schelling Segregation.


DONE: Simulation of Schelling Segregation.

